intheforex.com 2013-06-01

# Privacy Policy | InTheForex

INTHEFOREX.COM respects each individual's right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual client by providing you with security. The provisions of this notice apply to former members as well as our current members.

We collect a limited amount of information about our members, so that we can provide a site that is more interesting and useful, as well as provide advertising that is more appropriate for our readers. We ask for your name, e-mail address and other personal information when you register on INTHEFOREX.COM.

INTHEFOREX.COM shares your concern about the protection of your personal information online. INTHEFOREX.COM will not disclose any personal information to any third parties, except when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, to protect other users of INTHEFOREX.COM services, or to respond to an emergency.

INTHEFOREX.COM uses information obtained from its users to enhance users' experiences on our site. Tracking information is used to create aggregate reports on user demographics and site traffic patterns and then provided to our advertisers and partners, enabling them to better target their advertisements to our users. None of the information provided to them can be connected to the identities or other personal information of individual users.

INTHEFOREX.COM uses reasonable security methods to protect the data that resides on our servers. However, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our servers, nor can we guarantee that information that users supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.
